Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Computer Research in Music and Acoustics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
  - Studios, 1970s, 1980s
    - Colgate, D. Morrill, "Real Time Two-Way Multi-pass Digital Music System (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Computer Music Groups, 1980s and 1990
    - MuSIG members lists 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Computer Music Studios, Centers, 1990s
    - CNMAT-UC Berkeley, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Lists of Computer Music Centers (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - History of Computer Music-paper, 1989-1991
    - History of Computer Music-paper 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Computer Music Research-National
    - Olson, Harry F. (RCA) IEEE Spectrum "Electronic Music Synthesis for Recordings" 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Makhoul, J. IEEE 1974-1975 "Linear Prediction: a Tutorial Review" (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Beanchamp, J.W.: AES 1980, "Wind Instrument Analysis" (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Manoury, McAdams, Wessel 1984 Course Abstracts-Paris? (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Albert Bregman-McGill University (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Barry Truax (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Computer Music Research-International
    - University of Melbourne Computer Music Project. Conyngham, B.E. and Harris, R.P. "Computer Synthesis of String Timbre", 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - University of Melbourne Computer Music Project. Conyngham, B.E. and Harris, R.P. "Paradigms for Machine Assisted Composition", 1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Grenoble, France, Cadoz, Claude, "Le Rapport Instrumental dans l'ordinateur Applique a la Creation Musicale", no date (1980s) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Laske, Otto "Composition Theory:" about AI and Computer Music (unpublished) 1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - International Historic Papers
    - Utrecht, Netherlands, Laske, Otto, "Procedural Approaches to Music/Theory" (2 papers) 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Cadoz and Florens: Paper in French, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Holtzman, S.R., University of Edinburgh, "A Description of Automated Digital Sound Synthesis Instrument" April 1978 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Psychoacoustics and Music Psychology
    - "The Role of Psychoacoustics in Computer Music" author unknown-Pierce? No date. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Dr. M.F. Malik: Communication Analysis of Sound Information Complexes no date-late 1970s (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Pressing, Jeff: Cognitive Isomorphisms in Pitch and Rhythm in World Musics (no date) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Bruner, Jerome: "Organization of Early Skilled Action" March 1972 (Harvard and Oxford Universities) (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - S.M. Kosslyn, "Scanning Visual images:…" (Stanford) in Perception and Psychophysics 1992-1993. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Pierce, J.R., Lipers, R., and Cheetham, C. "Hearing" research abstract 3/1975 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Pisoni, David (Indiana University) Memory and Cognition "Auditory short-term memory an vowel perception" 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Pierce, J.R. and Zweig, G. on Hearing and Communication, Biosciences Communications, printed in Switzerland (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - McAdams, S. and Bregman, A "Hearing Musical Streams" CMJ 1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Gabrielsson, Alf, "Music Psychology…" Royal Swedish Academy of Music. February 1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Clynes, Manfred: "Computers and Expression in Music" 1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Vos, Joos, and Rasch, Rudolf in Perception and Psychophysics, 1981, "The Perceptual Onset of Muscial Tones" (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Rasch, Rudolf University of Utrecht August 1981 "theory of Beat Frequencies of Tempered Musical intervals and triads" (submitted to JASA) (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Rasch, Rudolf 2 papers 1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Vos, Joos (ICA Paris 1983) "Subjective Purity of Mistuned Musical Fifths and Major Thirds" (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Science News 12 1986 Diana Deutsch Experiment (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Roger Shepard-Psychology Professor wins Medal of Science September 1995 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Acoustic Research
    - Jon. F. Claerbout "Waveform Analysis" 1969 (Chevron Field Research) (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Jansson, E.V. "Acoustical measurements of the top plate vibrations of a guitar" in Acustica 1971 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Jansson, E.V. and Sandberg, J. "Long-time Average Spectra Applied to Analysis of Music" in Acustica 1975 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Jaffe, Acoustic Specialist, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Fielder, Louis-Amex Corp. 1981. "Dynamic-Range Requirement for Subjectively Noise-Free Reproduction of Music" (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Rasch, Randolph A. (Utrecht, Netherlands) 2 papers, 1983. Topics: Jitter in Voice and Violin Tones (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Kulowski, Andrzje: Acoustics of Dinkelspiel Auditorium. No date. (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - CCRMA Collaborative research
    - Harmony and New Scales-Matthews, Pierce, and Roberts (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - J. Chowning and M. Bresnick (Draft-1971) "A Preliminary Report: Frequency Modulation in the Audio Band" (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Grey and Moorer " Perceptual Evaluations of Synthesized musical Instruments" 1977, NEA and NSF Support (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Chafe, Mont-Renaud, Rush 1982, "Towards and Intelligent Editor of Digital Audio" (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Foster, S, Schloss W.A., Rockmore, J., MIT-CMJ 1982, "Toward an Intelligent Editor of Digital Audio: Signal Processing Methods" (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Karplus, K. and Strong, A., CMJ-MIT 1983, "Digital Synthesis of Plucked…" (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Jaffe, D., Smith, J.O.-CMJ, MIT 1983. "Extensions of the Karplus-Strong Plucked…" (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Friedlander, B and Smith, J.O. "Notch Filter" IEEE 1984 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Gordon, J. an Smith, Julius, ICMC 1985, "A Sine Generation Algorithm…" (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Mont-Reynaud, B. and Goldstein, M., ICMC 1985, "Rhythm Patterns" (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Marks, Joseph and Polito, John "Modeling Piano Tones" ICMC 1986. (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Dannenberg, R. and Mont-Reynaud. B., ICMC 1987, "Improvisation…" (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Mellinger, D., Garnett, G., and Mont-Reynaud, B., 1989, "Virtual Digital Design" (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Morrill, Dexter, and Cook, Perry, August 1989, on "Real-time Improvised Solo Trumpet" STAN-M-56 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Jaffe, D. and Boynton, L., CMJ NeXT 1989, "Sound and Music kits in NeXT" (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Serra, X. and Smith, J., CMJ 1990, "Spectral Modeling Synthesis" (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Authors A-B
    - Borish, Jeffrey, The Audio Amateur Jan. 1983, "A Digital Delay Line" Parts 1 and 2 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Borish, J. and Angell, J.B., J. Audio Eng. Soc. July/Aug. 1983, "An Efficent Algorithm for measuring the Impulse Response Using Pseudorandom Noise" (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Borish, Jeffery, 74th Audio Eng. Soc. Convention, "An Auditorium Simulator for Home Use" (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Borish, Jeffery, JASA June 1984, "Extension of the Image Model to arbitrary polyhedra (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Chowning, John
    - John Chowning-early research papers (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Cook, Perry
    - Cook, Perry (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Garnett/Gordon/Grey
    - Garnett/Gordon/Grey (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Keislar, Douglas
    - Keislar, Douglas, "Software for Real-Time Microtonal Control" (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - LeBrun/Lo/Loy
    - Lebrun, Marc (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Lo, Yee-On (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Loy, D. Gareth (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Mathews, Max
    - Mathews, Max (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - McAdams, Stephen
    - McAdams, Stephen (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Mont-Reynaud, B.
    - Mont-Reynaud, B. (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Moore, F.R.
    - Moore, F.R. (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Moorer, James
    - Moorer, James [1 of 4] (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Moorer, James [2 of 4] (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Moorer, James [3 of 4] (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Moorer, James [4 of 4] (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Muller, Carl
    - Muller, Carl "Measurement of Reverberation Time in the Variable Reverberation Time Room" (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Pierce, John
    - Pierce, John (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Samson, Peter
    - Samson, Peter, "A General Purpose Digital Synthesizer" (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Schottstaedt, Bill
    - Schottstaedt, Bill (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Smith, Julius
    - Smith, Julius [1 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Smith, Julius [2 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Smith, Julius [3 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Smith, L. (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Smith, L.
    - Suite for Trio 1977 L. Smith Using MS Program (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Strawn, J.
    - Strawn, J. [1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Strawn, J. [2 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Pierce, John
    - John R. Pierce, The Science of Musical Sound, 1st ed. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Review of The Science of Musical Sound (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - "J.R. Pierce Bibliography and Much, Much More" March 26, 1995 [1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "J.R. Pierce Bibliography and Much, Much More" March 26, 1995 [2 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - John Pierce receives Japan prize February 14, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Pierce Paper-Consonance and Harmony (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - John R Pierce Photos (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - J. Pierce-Science of Sound Letters-1983-1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - John Pierce wins Draper Prize, Nat. Academy of Engineering 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - J. Pierce: Essay, "Communication, Communication Sciences and Art" (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Pierce, Cook, Mathews, Shepard, Book of Lectures, 1993, Letters, proposals to Stanford (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Music V Manual
    - Mathews, Max, The Technology of Computer Sound Generation and Processing, Chapter 1- Fundamentals (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Mathews, Max, The Technology of Computer Sound Generation and Processing, Chapter 2- A Sequence of Tutorial Examples of Sound Generation (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Mathews, Max, The Technology of Computer Sound Generation and Processing, Chapter 3- Music V Manual (1) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Mathews, Max, The Technology of Computer Sound Generation and Processing, Chapter 3- Music V Manual (2) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Historic Papers, Mathews and Others, 1960s, 1970s
    - Max Mathews "An Acoustic Compiler for Music and Psychological Stimuli Nov. 1960 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Max Mathews "The Digital Computer as a Musical Instrument" 1963 (Nov) (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Mathews, M.V. and Moore, R. "Groove-a Program to Compose, Store, and Edit Functions of Time" 1970 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mathews, Pierce, and Guttman 1961-2, "Musical Sounds from Digital Computers" (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Pierce, Mathews and Risset, Nov 1965, "Further Experiments on the Use of the Computer in Connection with Music" (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Mathews and Guttman, no date, "Generation of Music by a Digital Computer (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Max Mathews Historical Papers
    - Max Mathews, Articles 1960-1963, Letter- J. Pierce (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - M.V. Mathews Research Papers (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Max Mathews- List of Publications (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Max Mathews- Essays on Theory and Computer Music (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Articles on Max Mathews-his ideas, inventions, etc. 1970s. (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Computer Music, Acoustics Articles arranged alphabetically by author Music
    - Anders Askenfelt and Erik V. Jansson (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - A.J. Bomans, L. Brothers and G. L. Shaw (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Magdalene H. Chalikia and Albert S. Bregman, Gunilla Carlsson et al. (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Stanley A. Erickson, Jr. (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Anders Friberg et al. (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Patricia Gramming, Johan Sundberg, Leif Akerlund (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Stellan Hertgard, Jan Gauffin, John Sundberg; Hynek Hermansky (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Erik V. Jansson, Asa Nilsonne and Joan Sundberg, Jean-Marc Jot and Antoine Chaigne (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Vladamir Komarov (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Von W. Lottermoser, Xiaodan Leng and Gordon L. Shaw and Eric L. Wright (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Stephan McAdams and Xavier Rodet, M.E. McIntyre and J. Woodhouse (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Nils-Erik Molin and Anders O. Wahlin (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Gordon L. Shaw et al., Johan Sundberg et al. (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Sten Ternstrom (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Neal F. Viemeister and Sid P. Bacon (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Gabriel Weinreich and Rene Causse (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Sound catalogue, Jean-Claude Risset, 1969
    - Jean-Claude Risset, 1969, "An Introductory Catalogue of Computer Synthesized Sounds" (first edition) (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Jean-Claude Risset, 1992, "My 1969 sound catalogue: looking back" and "An Introductory Catalogue of Computer Synthesized Sounds" (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Jean-Claude Risset, 1992 Sounds Catalogue draft with corrections (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Jean-Claude Risset, 1992, "My 1969 Sound catalogue: looking back" (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Jean-Claude Risset, 1992, "An Introductory Catalogue of Computer Synthesized Sounds" draft with Corrections (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - faxed draft of sound catalogue, 18 Nov. 1992 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - History of Computer Music and Risset's Introductory Sounds Catalogue
    - History of Computer Music and Risset's Introductory Sound Catalogue [1 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - History of Computer Music and Risset's Introductory Sound Catalogue [2 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - History of Computer Music and Risset's Introductory Sound Catalogue [3 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Jean Claude Risset, correspondence (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Floppy disks-Risset sound catalogue (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Manuals (Box 16)
  - Metal-bound programs (Box 17)
  - Knoll refurbishing (Box 17)
  - Computer files and audiovisual material (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Program FM Audio MII Master (Cam 2), 1988 Dec. 17; 0 (Box 18)
    - SW0087, 1980 Dec.; 0 (Box 18)
    - untitled AMPEX Videocassette, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Telegram (Dyaxis) DAJ, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 1a, 1988 April 15; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Diptych #2, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Tape 3a Dex-CD, 1988 April 16; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Diptych 1, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Solera Tunings New Piece, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 3b, 1988 April 16; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Tape 4b, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Tape 7a Schindler, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Quadro Tape Part, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Diptych Computer Part (Copy) No Clicks!, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Marrill: Quartet for Violin, Cello, & Loudspeakers; Schindler: Tremor of Night and Day, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Tape 4a, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Tape 5b, 1988 April 17; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Tape 6b, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - Tape 2b, 1988 April 15; 1 videotape(s) (Beta) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 1 Iso Reel; #3, T.C.I. Audio 2 Master, 1988 Dec. 17; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 1 Iso Reel; #2 T.C.I. Audio 2 Master, 1988 Dec. 17; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 1 Iso Reel; #1 T.C.I. Audio 2 Master, 1988 Dec. 17; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 2 Iso Reel; #3 T.C.I. Audio 2 Master, 1988 Dec. 17; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 2 Iso Reel; #2 T.C.I. Audio 2 Master, 1988 Dec. 17; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 18)
    - CCRMA Tape 2 Iso Reel; #1 T.C.I. Audio 2 Master, 1988 Dec. 17; 1 videotape(s) (U-matic) (Box 18)
    - Music from Mathematics, 1962; 1 phonograph record(s)
      Decca ‎– DL 79103 (Stereo) Produced by Bell Telephone Laboratories (1957-91). Played by IBM computer and digital to sound transducer. Program notes by Max V. Mathews and B. Deutschman.
      Tracklist:
      A1 Unknown Artist – Frère Jacques A2 Orlando Gibbons – Fantasia A3 Max Mathews – Bicycle Built For Two A4 John Robinson Pierce – Molto Amoroso A5 John Robinson Pierce – Variations In Timbre And Attack A6 John Robinson Pierce – Stochatta A7 John Robinson Pierce – Five Against Seven (Random Canon) A8 John Robinson Pierce – Beat Canon A9 John Robinson Pierce – Melodie A10 Max Mathews – Numerology B1 Max Mathews – The Second Law B2 Max Mathews – May Carol B3 S.D. Speeth – Theme And Variations B4 David Lewin (2) – Study No.1 B5 David Lewin (2) – Study No.2 B6 Newman Guttman – Pitch Variations B7 James Tenney – Noise Study B8 Max Mathews – Joy To The World
  - IRCAM (and McGill) Sound Library-videotapes (Box 19)
  - Acoustics (emulation)
    - Jansson, Bork, & Meyer (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bekesy (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Lindquist & Sundberg (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Fransson & Sundberg, & Tjernlund (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Engel, Kenneth (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Analysis--Study (classics)
    - Dawn, Rilen (empty) (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sundberg (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Auditory Patterns
    - Perceptual org. of nine-element auditory temporal patters (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Massaro (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Carterette, Edward (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cerebral Asymmetry Lusted
    - Dichotic Melody (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Alf Gabrielsson
    - Alf Gabrielsson (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Catalogues/Advertising
    - Distribution Magnetique [empty] (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Computer Software/Hardware
    - Miller, James A. [empty] (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Computer Music
    - Computer Technology (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Pope, Stephen T. [empty] (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Conversations Around the Pacific Ring (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Morril [empty] (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Hiller [empty] (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Clough [empty] (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Amspoker [empty] (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Articles (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Digital Synthesis
    - Digital Synthesis (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Distance
    - Leitner: Sound achitecture (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Articles (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Dowling
    - Dowling papers I (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Dowling papers II (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Dowling III (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Ears Manual (I know it's absurd!)
    - Karlsson, Jansson (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Echo/Reverb/Prec.
    - Moorer, James A. (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Gen: (Y)ac & Music
    - Winkel: (Y)ac (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - (Y) Physics: Wickelgrew (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Ward: Music Perc (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Gestalt
    - Garner: Good patterns (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Grammar
    - Lindblom: grammer of music (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Erickson, Robert (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Communications of the ACML (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Restle: sequential learning [empty] (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Seeger (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Simon: PATT in M. [empty] (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Suppets: Prob. Grammar [empty] (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Becker: Anatomy of a mode [empty] (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Attne Ave - Stochastic Comp (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Harwood [empty] (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Harwood [empty] (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Laske [empty] (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Holtzman [empty] (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Intervals
    - Perception of musical intervals (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Levelt, Geer, Plomp (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Burton (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Grey, John (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - JAM
    - JAM (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Lateralization
    - Guttman: Binaural click lateralization maps (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Sayers: image lateralization (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Hafter: lateralization of tones & clicks (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Mills: hi-f lateralization (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Mousheghan: lateralzn low-f (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Lateralization & internsity disc. Elfner (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Deatherage: lingual interaction (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Auditory perspective (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - DAVID: Binaural interaction (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Various figures
    - Various figures (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - JASA 2/3 MDS Studies, 1976
    - JASA 2/3 MDS Studies 1976 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - JASA 1 Reviewers
    - JASA 1 Reviewers (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Publish & Perish
    - ABAS papers (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Don, etc.
    - Don, etc. (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Matthews
    - Mills: localization in Tobias (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Shepard, Roger N. (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Articles (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Pierce, John (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Cognition/Memory
    - Bower, Gordon H. (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Misc. (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Rothenberg (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Membranophones
    - Craig Woodson (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Risset's Catalog (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Cage, John (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Musical Cognition
    - Laske (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Musical Performance
    - Sundberg (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Naval Research--London
    - Naval Research - London (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Perception--General
    - Arnold, Peter; Bowser, Gordon (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Bamberger, Jeanne (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Chistovich (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Cohen, Elizabeth Ann (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Dowling (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Gray, John Michael (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Levin, David (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hartmann, W. M. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Audition re. Vision - Julesz, Hirsh (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Huggins (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Plomp (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Schouten (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Schroeder (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Perception
    - Ritsma, R.J. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Spencer (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Wightman (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Sound constructs (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Shepard
    - Shepard (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Speech Perc.
    - Askerfelt (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Broadbent, Donald (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Colarusso (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Liberman - Speech Code (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Mattingly - Speech (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Pisoni (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Slawson: Vowel quality & timbre (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Schloss (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Pols, L.C.W. (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Speech Understanding: Erman, Lee; Hayes-Roth; Lesser/Reddy (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Walker, Donald E.: Speech Understanding Research (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Baker, James K. (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Speech Research and Instrumentation
    - Speech Research and Instrumentation (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Pitch
    - Houtsma- Pitch (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Licklider - Periodicity/Autocorr (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Autocorrelation (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Wightman - Pitch (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Terhardt (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Yost (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Pitch perception (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Shepard, Roger N. (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Psychology--Acoustics
    - Goldsmith (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Anderson, Mark R. (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Nilsonne, Sundberg (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Coons (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Carrol, J. Douglas (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Keil, Charles M. H. (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Sherburne, Donald W. (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Shepard, R. N. (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Somatics (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Misc. Research (P-Z) by subject (Box 22)
  - John Grey: Research data, instruments, etc. (Box 23)
  - John Grey (Box 24)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH.2013-082
  - Music From Mathematics: Played by IBM 7090 Computer and Digital to Sound Transducer, 1962; 1.1; 1 phonograph record(s) (Box 1)
- Records
Subject Index
1969 sound catalogue, Jean-Claude Risset 15
1974 NEA Proposals Computer Music Facility 1
1974-1975 NEA Grant for Center 1
Acoustic Research 14
Acoustics (emulation) 20
Alf Gabrielsson 20
Analysis--Study (classics) 20
Argentina Exchange Admin. Documents (Rockefeller) 2
Argentina Exchange Rockefeller 2
Art-Music collaborations 10
Audio Processors [No folders] 20
Auditory Patterns 20
Authors A-P 14-15
Bourges 10
Buenos Aires LIPM 10
California Arts Council (CAC) 3